pycomall.com 2013-06-05

# Pycomall - Buy Sell Digital Contents

In order to provide uninterrupted services to you as a visitor or a user of our site, Pycomall, it is necessary that you provide us with your complete and correct personal information ("Personal Data") when you are applying to us and/or continue to subscribe with us for service(s) and/or product(s) ("Services").

Your Personal Data shall be strictly kept confidential at all times which have been and will be our policies and practices with respect to the use, collection, retention, transfer, disclosure, security and access of Personal Data.

Unless otherwise stated, only your visit to Pycomall will be recorded, but not your personally identifiable information, or information that is about you and identifies you. Using of Cookies* (if any) in any part of this web site will not be directed for collecting your personally identifiable information.

You may choose not to accept Cookies by resetting the relevant Internet options or the properties of your computer system's browsers. However, by doing so, you may not be able to optimize the usage of, or enable, certain functions made available in our web sites.

On occasion, you may be required to provide us with your personally identifiable information including, but not limited to, your name, gender, age, address, telephone number, fax number, email address, credit card information, bank account number, education level, occupation etc. Refusal to provide such information may made it impossible for you to access certain parts of our web site, or may hinder our handling of any application or request you are submitting, or may otherwise abort the objectives of your visit.

Once you have furnish us with your personally identifiable information, you may receive emails containing promotional materials or announcements from us from time to time.

Our web site may host various on-line stores or service providers, which are operated by third party merchants. Should you ever use or order any services or products from any of them, please keep in mind that any information you provide, once transferred to the relevant merchant, is beyond our control and thus outside the scope of protection afforded by us.

You agree that, by providing us with your Personal Data, you allow us to use and retain your Personal Data for the following purposes and for other purposes as shall be agreed between you and us or required by law from time to time:

(a) Provisioning the Services;  
(b) Marketing of the Services related goods and/or services by us, our agents or our subsidiaries;  
(c) Analyzing, verifying and/or checking of your credit, payment and/or status in relation to the provision of the Services;  
(d) Processing of any payment instructions, direct debit facilities and/or credit facilities requested by you;  
(e) Enabling the daily operation of your account and/or the collection of amounts outstanding in your account in relation to the Services;  
(f) Processing of any benefits stemming from or in connection with the Services.

In relating to the mentioned purposes above, you also accept our disclosure and transferring to any third party service providers, any credit providers, banks, financial institutions, any third party collection agencies, any credit reference agencies, any security agencies, our agents, contractors, our professional advisers, any other persons under a duty of confidentiality to us and any of our actual or proposed assignees or transferees of our rights with respect to you of using, disclosing, processing, holding, retaining or transferring such Personal Data.

In case we deemed it necessary, we reserve the right to amend this Statement without prior notice. So, regular checking for any amendments is advisable.
